你才臭气熏天呢
You're a band smell!
抱歉  抱歉  把垃圾放在这就行
Sorry. Sorry. Just pile these here.
去清理更多的垃圾箱吧
Go empty more cans.
很快就会有卡车来把这些垃圾运走的
The truck will be here soon to take this.
欧文  那是罗斯塔姆的卡车
Oh, Owen, that's Rostam's truck,
他堵在环城大道上了
and he's stuck in traffic on the Belt Parkway.
一小时后才能到  游客们都开始吃午饭了
That's over an hour away. People are starting to eat lunch!
-你们知道午饭之后是什么吗
- Do you know what happens after lunch?
-午睡  -晚饭
- Nap time. - Dinner!
餐盒  数不清的餐盒
Packaging. So much packaging.
欧文  如果来了一大车旅客给垃圾拍照
Owen, is it bad if a busload of tourists just pulled up
-是不是不太好  -是
- and started taking pictures of the trash? - Yes.
那如果刚来了三大车旅客是不是就更糟了
So it's worse if three busloads just pulled up?
说"贝琪"  "贝琪"
Say "Bitsy". "Bitsy".
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
保洁员拒绝打扫
The housekeeping staff is refusing to clean